(yue)嗰一日
(en)That day
(yue)人類記返起…
(en)Humans remembered...
(yue)一直畀佢哋支配嘅恐懼
(en)The fear that had always ruled over them
(yue)同有如韞喺鳥籠入面嘅…
(en)And the humiliation of being trapped in a birdcage-like state...
(yue)屈辱
(en)Humiliation
(yue)準備作戰
(en)Prepare for battle
(yue)目標第一個，一定要將佢殺死
(en)The first target, make sure to kill it
(yue)務必令到呢度變化我哋人類一牆外嘅據點
(en)Ensure this place becomes humanity's foothold beyond the walls
(yue)目標接近
(en)The target is approaching
(yue)同訓練嗰陣一樣兵分兩路
(en)Just like training, split into two groups
(yue)照計劃由我哋呢組做餌
(en)As planned, our group will act as bait
(yue)攻擊組即刻進行立體機動攻擊
(en)The attack group will launch a three-dimensional maneuver attack immediately
(yue)全部位同時攻擊
(en)Attack all positions simultaneously
(yue)就畀你見識下我哋人類嘅…
(en)Let me show you humanity's...
(yue)力量！
(en)Power!
(yue)《致二千年後的你：西甘希娜淪陷1》
(en)“To You, 2000 Years Later: The Fall of Shiganshina Part 1”
(yue)係…米卡莎
(en)It’s… Mikasa
(yue)我哋要返去喇
(en)We need to go back
(yue)你點會喺度𠸏？
(en)What are you doing here?
(yue)你係唔係到而家都仲未瞓醒啊？
(en)Are you still not awake yet?
(yue)唔係，不過…
(en)No, but…
(yue)我好似發咗個好長同埋好恐怖嘅夢
(en)I think I had a long and terrifying dream
(yue)夢見啲咩呢？
(en)What did you dream about?
(yue)諗唔起啊
(en)I can’t remember
(yue)艾倫，你做咩喊啊？
(en)Eren, why are you crying?
(yue)（845年，西甘希娜）
(en)(Year 845, Shiganshina)
(yue)記住
(en)Remember
(yue)城牆係由神嘅智慧興建出嚟㗎
(en)The walls were built by God’s wisdom
(yue)所以城牆就係神喺世上施嘅神跡
(en)So the walls are God’s miracle on Earth
(yue)無論係邊個，都絕對唔可以沾污城牆
(en)No one is allowed to defile the walls
(yue)唔准同你講啊
(en)You can’t tell anyone
(yue)邊個都絕對唔講得
(en)Don’t tell anyone, no matter who
(yue)我知喇
(en)I understand
(yue)但係，你無端端流眼淚
(en)But suddenly you started crying
(yue)不如叫你爸爸睇下啦
(en)How about letting your dad take a look?
(yue)正蠢材
(en)That’s stupid
(yue)咁尷尬，唔會啲點同爸爸講
(en)That’s embarrassing, no way I’d tell Dad
(yue)做咩流眼淚啊？艾倫
(en)Why are you crying, Eren?
(yue)漢尼斯叔叔
(en)Uncle Hannes
(yue)你係咪發米卡莎嘅脾氣啊？
(en)Did you upset Mikasa?
(yue)你唔知，唔好亂講啦
(en)You don’t know, don’t talk nonsense
(yue)好大𠹻酒𡃴啊
(en)What a drunkard
(yue)得閒飲返杯真係過癮
(en)Having a drink when free is really enjoyable
(yue)佢哋又係噉
(en)There they go again
(yue)你想唔想過嚟一齊飲啊？
(en)Do you want to come drink with us?
(yue)唔好，你今日負責咩啊？
(en)No, what’s your duty today?
(yue)我？負責守城門喇
(en)Me? Guarding the gate
(yue)成日流流長，又無所事事
(en)Always idling around, doing nothing
(yue)梗係覺得肚餓又會口渴㗎喇
(en)Of course, you’d feel hungry and thirsty
(yue)好似噉樣加少少酒落嘢飲都冇所謂喇
(en)Adding a bit of alcohol to your drink is fine
(yue)橫掂我哋都冇嘢好做
(en)We have nothing else to do anyway
(yue)萬一有事發生，你哋都做戰鬥到咩？
(en)If something happens, can you even fight?
-到底會有咩事發生啊？
-仲使問？
(en)-What could possibly happen?
-Do you even need to ask?
(yue)嗰啲嘢破壞城牆走入嚟就要靠你哋收拾㗎喇
(en)If those things break through the walls, it’ll be up to you to handle them
(yue)呢條魚好新鮮㗎
(en)This fish is really fresh
(yue)復咗嚟
(en)I just caught it
(yue)喂，艾倫
(en)Hey, Eren
(yue)咪失驚無神大聲嗌啊
(en)Stop shouting all of a sudden
(yue)醫生個仔好活潑喎
(en)The doctor’s son is really energetic
(yue)如果佢哋真係可以攻入城牆裏面嘅
我哋收會收拾佢哋
(en)If they really invade the walls, we’ll deal with them
(yue)之不過你擔心嘅呢一種事
(en)But the thing you’re worried about
(yue)根本成百年以嚟都冇發生過
(en)Hasn’t happened in a hundred years
(yue)我爸爸話：
“意外通常發生係人最安心鬆懈嘅時候
唔可以大意㗎”
(en)My dad says:
"Disasters happen when people are most relaxed.
You can’t let your guard down.”
(yue)乜醫生噉樣講過咩？
(en)The doctor really said that?
(yue)噉實有佢嘅道理
(en)There must be some truth to it
(yue)話晒佢以前都醫返好晒呢一度患咗流行病嘅人
(en)After all, he once cured everyone here of an epidemic
(yue)佢當然叻過我好多喇
(en)He’s obviously much smarter than me
(yue)不過對嗰啲嘢嘅認識就例外
(en)But his knowledge about those things is an exception
(yue)我當咗兵之後
有陣時要輪流幫城牆做例行維修工作
(en)After becoming a soldier,
I sometimes help with routine wall maintenance
(yue)所以見過嗰啲嘢喺外邊行
(en)So I’ve seen those things walking outside
(yue)我唔認為佢哋有能力破壞
或者嗰度呢一大幅有成50米高嘅牆
(en)I don’t think they can destroy
this massive 50-meter-high wall
(yue)唔通
(en)Unless…
(yue)你哋一直以嚟從來都冇諗過同嗰啲嘢戰鬥？
(en)Have you never thought of fighting those things?
(yue)梗係冇喇
(en)Of course not
(yue)有冇搞錯？
(en)Are you kidding me?
(yue)噉你哋班人仲叫咩駐紮兵團啊？
(en)How can you still call yourselves the Garrison Regiment?
(yue)索性叫城牆維修隊吖
(en)Might as well call yourselves the Wall Repair Team
(yue)個名叫好聽喎
(en)It’s a fitting name, isn’t it?
(yue)不過，艾倫，你要明白
(en)But, Eren, you need to understand
(yue)需要士兵出動嘅時候就代表情況變得好惡劣
(en)When soldiers are needed, it means things have turned dire
(yue)相反當士兵畀人笑
(en)On the contrary, when soldiers are mocked
(yue)遊手好閒、白逗人工、一無是處
(en)For being idle and useless freeloaders
(yue)就代表大家生活安穩
(en)It means everyone is living in peace
(yue)即係…
(en)So that means...
(yue)就算一世走唔出城牆
(en)Even if we never leave the walls our entire lives
(yue)只要有得食同瞓就夠？
(en)As long as we have food and sleep, that’s enough?
(yue)但係，咁簡直就係…
(en)But that’s just...
(yue)同安全嘅畜生冇分別
(en)No different from being safe livestock
(yue)呢個細路講嘢就好有種
(en)This kid talks so boldly
(yue)自己就咩都做唔到
(en)Yet he can’t do anything himself
(yue)係咪係啊，漢尼斯？
(en)Isn’t that right, Hannes?
(yue)哦，係啊
(en)Oh, yeah
(yue)喂！艾倫！
(en)Hey! Eren!
(yue)古靈精怪
(en)You little rascal
(yue)唔通艾倫佢…
(en)Could it be that Eren...
(yue)大個之後想加入調查兵團？
(en)Wants to join the Scout Regiment when he grows up?
(yue)艾倫，你都係唔好加入調查兵團啊
(en)Eren, you really shouldn’t join the Scout Regiment
(yue)點解啊？
(en)Why?
(yue)唔通你呢度睇唔起調查兵團？
(en)Don’t tell me you look down on the Scouts?
(yue)呢個根本就唔係睇唔睇得起嘅問題
(en)This isn’t about respect or lack of it
(yue)調查兵團，佢哋返嚟喇
(en)The Scouts, they’re back
(yue)城牆嘅大門要打開
(en)The gates of the wall need to open
(yue)行啦，米卡莎，我哋迎接英雄
(en)Let’s go, Mikasa. Let’s welcome the heroes
(yue)咁多人嘅，睇唔到𠻹
(en)There’s so many people, I can’t see
(yue)一大班人去到返咁少人返
(en)A large group went out, but so few returned
(yue)慌唔係畀嗰啲嘢食咗咩
(en)Could they have been eaten by those things?
(yue)無情情走咗城牆外邊
(en)Going outside the walls recklessly
(yue)就會有噉個下場呢
(en)Leads to an end like this
(yue)莫杰斯…
(en)Moses...
(yue)請問咁多位
(en)Excuse me, everyone
(yue)你哋有冇見過我仔莫杰斯啊？
(en)Have you seen my son Moses?
(yue)我仔而家到底喺邊度啊？
(en)Where is my son right now?
(yue)你就係莫杰斯嘅媽媽？
(en)Are you Moses’s mother?
(yue)你畀佢
(en)Give this to her
(yue)真係好對唔住，我哋只係帶到咁多返嚟
(en)I’m so sorry, this is all we could bring back
(yue)不過…我個仔真係好有用
(en)But... my son was truly useful
(yue)就算個冇直接粒都咩功都冇關係
(en)Even if he didn’t contribute directly, it doesn’t matter
(yue)我個仔莫杰斯嘅死係唔係…
(en)Didn’t my son Moses’s death...
(yue)對人類第日嘅反攻有好大貢獻啊
(en)Make a huge contribution to humanity’s future counterattack?
(yue)咁當然係喇
(en)Of course, it did
(yue)唔係
(en)No
(yue)我哋呢一次調查…
(en)This time on the expedition...
(yue)我哋…
(en)We...
(yue)仍然…
(en)Still...
(yue)仲係…
(en)Remain...
(yue)我哋呢一次調查仍然係冇成果啊
(en)This expedition still yielded no results
(yue)一切都係因為我冇能
(en)It’s all because of my incompetence
(yue)令到好多士兵白白噉犧牲
(en)That so many soldiers died in vain
(yue)到而家都仲係唔知道…
(en)Even now, we still don’t know...
(yue)佢哋嘅真面目係點樣
(en)What their true nature is
(yue)我哋根本咩都查唔到啊
(en)We haven’t found out anything at all
(yue)真係好陰功啊
(en)It’s truly a tragedy
(yue)話咗㗎喇
(en)I already said it
(yue)調查兵團出去做乜嘢啊？
(en)What’s the point of the Scouts going out there?
(yue)我哋交稅養啲噉個人啊，我哋仲應該…
(en)We pay taxes to support these people, and we’re supposed to...
(yue)做咩啊，細路？做咩打我？
(en)What’s wrong, kid? Why did you hit me?
(yue)喂
(en)Hey
(yue)放開我，米卡莎！
(en)Let me go, Mikasa!
(yue)喂，細路，你咪走啊，細路
(en)Hey, kid, don’t run, kid
(yue)米卡莎，放開我吖！
(en)Mikasa, let me go!
(yue)你到底做咩啊？
(en)What are you doing?
(yue)搞到我跌晒啲柴喇
(en)You made me drop all the firewood
(yue)艾倫
(en)Eren
(yue)你到而家都仲係好想加入調查兵團
(en)You still want to join the Scout Regiment
(yue)係唔係啊？
(en)Don’t you?
(yue)可唔可以幫手執啊？
(en)Can you help me pick these up?
(yue)咁小事都要幫？
(en)Do you even need help with such a small thing?
(yue)（而家可以公開嘅情報關於牆壁1）
（人類喺三幅城牆內生活）
(en)(Now Public Information About the Walls 1)
(Humans live within three walls)
(yue)（第一幅叫瑪莉亞之牆）
（第二幅叫露絲之牆）
（第三幅叫仙娜）
(en)(The first is Wall Maria)
(The second is Wall Rose)
(The third is Wall Sina)
(yue)（而家可以公開嘅情報關於牆壁2）
（牆壁之間嘅面積大致相等）
(en)(Now Public Information About the Walls 2)
(The areas between the walls are roughly equal)
(yue)（瑪莉亞同露絲之間距離100公里）
（露絲同仙娜之間距離130公里）
（仙娜同中心點距離250公里）
(en)(The distance between Maria and Rose is 100 km)
(The distance between Rose and Sina is 130 km)
(The distance from Sina to the center is 250 km)
(yue)我哋返嚟喇
(en)We’re back
(yue)你哋返嚟喇
(en)You’re back
(yue)好嘢喎，艾倫
(en)Good job, Eren
(yue)今日咁勤力執到咁多柴啊？
(en)You worked so hard today to collect this much firewood?
(yue)哦，係啊
(en)Oh, yeah
(yue)做咩掹我耳仔啊？
(en)Why are you pulling my ear?
(yue)你啲耳仔紅晒喇，證明你有嘢瞞住我
(en)Your ears are all red, proving you’re hiding something from me
(yue)啲柴係唔係米卡莎執嘎？
(en)Wasn’t the firewood collected by Mikasa?
(yue)爸爸又要出門呀？
(en)Dad is going out again?
-有嘢要做？
-係啊
(en)-Is there something you need to do?
-Yes
(yue)我要去內陸應診
(en)I have to go to the interior for a consultation
(yue)大概去兩三日到喇
(en)I’ll be gone for about two or three days
(yue)艾倫話大個之後要加入調查兵團
(en)Eren said he wants to join the Scout Regiment when he grows up
-米卡莎，做乜嘢講？
-艾倫
(en)-Mikasa, why did you say that?
-Eren
(yue)你個腦諗緊啲乜嘢啊？
(en)What are you thinking?
(yue)你知唔知道有幾多人走出城牆外面
結果搞到自己連命都冇埋？
(en)Do you know how many people left the walls
only to end up losing their lives?
(yue)我梗係知喇
(en)Of course I know
-係噉點解？
-艾倫
(en)-Then why?
-Eren
(yue)點解你想走出到個城牆外面？
(en)Why do you want to go outside the walls?
(yue)因為我想知道
(en)Because I want to know
(yue)城牆外面嘅世界到底係點樣
(en)What the world outside the walls is really like
(yue)我唔想一世咩都唔知根本喺城牆入面
(en)I don’t want to spend my life knowing nothing inside these walls
(yue)而且…
(en)And...
(yue)冇人繼續調查兵團嘅工作
(en)If no one continues the Scouts’ work
(yue)噉之前為咗人類而死嘅人就會白白犧牲！
(en)Then the people who died for humanity will have sacrificed in vain!
(yue)我明白喇
(en)I understand
(yue)我夠鐘搭船，我要出去喇
(en)It’s time for me to board the ship, I have to go
(yue)等陣啊，老公，你勸阿艾倫吖
(en)Wait, dear, you should talk to Eren
(yue)卡露拉，人類擁有嘅好奇心…
(en)Carla, humanity’s curiosity...
(yue)並唔會因為其他人三言兩語就可以撳得住
(en)Can’t be suppressed by a few words from others
(yue)艾倫
(en)Eren
(yue)我返嚟之後，就帶你去過間
(yue)直冇帶你去過個地下室喇
(en)When I come back, I’ll take you to the basement
(en)I’ve never taken you to before
(yue)你講真𠸏？
(en)Are you serious?
(yue)早去早回吖
(en)Go and come back soon
(yue)我唔批准
(en)I don’t approve
(yue)我唔會畀你咁蠢加入調查兵團
(en)I won’t let you foolishly join the Scout Regiment
(yue)你話噉樣係蠢？
(en)You think that’s foolish?
(yue)我話嗰啲
(en)I’m saying those
(yue)甘於過安穩生活做畜牲嘅人至係蠢吖
(en)Who are content living as safe livestock are the foolish ones
(yue)艾倫
(en)Eren
(yue)米卡莎
(en)Mikasa
(yue)你都知艾倫份人好容易闖禍
(en)You know Eren gets into trouble easily
(yue)所以麻煩你幫我睇住佢
(en)So I need you to watch over him
(yue)唔好畀佢出事啊
(en)Make sure he stays safe
(yue)點啊，異端？
(en)What’s wrong, heretic?
(yue)你唔服氣嘅就快還手啦
(en)If you’re upset, fight back already
(yue)我先至唔會做啲噉樣嘅事啊
(en)I would never do something like that
(yue)否則我就會同你哋一樣講野蠻
(en)Otherwise, I’d be as barbaric as you
(yue)講咩話？
(en)What did you say?
(yue)你哋喺心入面其實以為我講嘅嘢係啱嘅
(en)Deep down, you know I’m right
(yue)因為拗唔贏我所以你哋先出手打我
(en)You hit me because you can’t win the argument
(yue)亦即係你哋一早已經向我投咗降
(en)That means you’ve already surrendered to me
(yue)收聲吖，你唔好再狡辯吖！
(en)Shut up, stop making excuses!
(yue)停手吖！
(en)Stop it!
(yue)艾倫啊
(en)Eren
(yue)嗰個蠢材自己送上門啝
(en)That idiot came right to us
(yue)我要打到佢甩牙
(en)I’m going to knock his teeth out
(yue)好好教訓到佢
(en)Teach him a proper lesson
(yue)係…係米卡莎
(en)It’s... it’s Mikasa
(yue)唔掂啊，快啲走啊！
(en)We’re in trouble, run!
(yue)走啊
(en)Run!
(yue)冇膽鬼
(en)Cowards
(yue)佢哋一見到我，就即刻走夾唔抖喇
(en)The moment they saw me, they ran away in panic
(yue)唔係啊，係見到米卡莎先走㗎
(en)No, they ran because they saw Mikasa
(yue)點啊，阿爾敏？
(en)What’s wrong, Armin?
(yue)我可以自己起身
(en)I can get up on my own
(yue)好啦
(en)Alright
(yue)噉跟住，我就同佢哋講
(en)So then, I told them
(yue)人類仲有一日會走出外面嘅世界
(en)One day, humanity will venture out into the world
(yue)我哋就打我，鬧我異端
(en)They hit me and called me a heretic
(yue)衰人
(en)Jerks
(yue)只不過係話要走出外面吒嘛
(en)I just said we should go outside
(yue)點解就要畀人歧視喎？
(en)Why does that make me a target?
(yue)係因為…
(en)Is it because...
(yue)喺牆入面嘅呢一百年
(en)In these hundred years inside the walls
(yue)大家嘅生活都過得好安穩
(en)Everyone has lived such peaceful lives
(yue)所以大家都驚派人出外面嘅話
(en)So they’re afraid that sending people outside
(yue)會將嗰啲嘢有外面引到牆入面
(en)Will attract those things from outside into the walls
(yue)而且國王政府一向方針
(en)And the government’s policy has always been
(yue)就係將去探索牆外面世界當係最大禁忌
(en)To treat exploring the outside world as the greatest taboo
(yue)要點用我哋自己條命
(en)How we use our lives
(yue)係我哋嘅自由
(en)Is our own freedom
(yue)我唔准你噉諗
(en)I won’t allow you to think like that
(yue)唔准
(en)No way
(yue)我都仲未話你啊
(en)I haven’t even started with you
(yue)竟然同我父母講
(en)You actually told my parents
(yue)你冇叫我隱瞞呢件事
(en)You never told me to keep it a secret
(yue)隱瞞咩啊？
(en)Keep what a secret?
(yue)嗰件事…
(en)That thing...
(yue)我而家冇心情講
(en)I’m not in the mood to talk about it now
(yue)係呀？噉就算喇
(en)Is that so? Then fine
(yue)講真…
(en)Honestly...
(yue)盲目相信城牆
(en)Blindly believing in the walls
(yue)可以永遠保護我哋嘅安全
(en)Can always keep us safe
(yue)真係太荒謬喇
(en)Is utterly absurd
(yue)就算城牆喺之前一百年都冇出過事
(en)Even if nothing happened to the walls in the past 100 years
(yue)都唔等於呢一大幅城牆
(en)It doesn’t mean these massive walls
(yue)今日唔會出事
(en)Won’t fail today
(yue)咩事啊？咩啊？
(en)What’s going on? What’s that?
(yue)好大聲啊
(en)It’s so loud
(yue)咩事啊？
(en)What happened?
(yue)係爆炸？
(en)Was that an explosion?
(yue)嗰度啊，好似有嘢跌落嚟啊
-過睇下
(en)Over there, something seems to have fallen
-Let’s go take a look
(yue)喂，等埋，阿爾敏
(en)Hey, wait up, Armin
(yue)咩事啊？
(en)What’s wrong?
(yue)大家企定定望緊啲咩啊？
(en)Why is everyone standing still staring?
(yue)唔係啩，幅牆…
(en)No way, the wall...
(yue)有成50米咁高㗎
(en)It’s 50 meters high
(yue)係嗰啲嘢
(en)It’s those things
(yue)係巨人
(en)It’s a Titan
(yue)城牆…
(en)The wall...
(yue)畀巨人踢穿咗個大窿
(en)Has been kicked open by a Titan
(yue)係巨人入進嚟啊！
(en)A Titan has entered!
(yue)走吖！
(en)Run!
(yue)快啲走啦
(en)Hurry up and run
(yue)艾倫
(en)Eren
(yue)係我屋企嗰邊啊
(en)It’s near my house
(yue)媽媽佢…
(en)Mom, she...
(yue)米卡莎…
(en)Mikasa...
(yue)已經…已經冇喇
(en)It’s... it’s already gone
(yue)呢個城市冇喇
(en)This city is gone
(yue)呢度好快就會畀嗰啲巨人侵佔啊！
(en)This place will soon be overrun by Titans!
(yue)唔好死吖
(en)Don’t die
(yue)千祈唔好𢱕中我屋企
(en)Please don’t hit my house
(yue)只要轉到個彎，就返到屋企！
(en)Just need to turn the corner, and I’ll be home!
(yue)媽媽！
(en)Mom!
-艾倫
-米卡莎，你幫我手抬嗰邊
(en)-Eren
-Mikasa, help me lift this side
(yue)一齊抬起條柱吖
(en)Lift the beam together
-要快啲啊，米卡莎
-知喇
(en)-Hurry up, Mikasa
-I got it
(yue)嗰啲巨人已經走咗入嚟啊
(en)The Titans have already entered
(yue)艾倫，你快啲帶米卡莎走
(en)Eren, take Mikasa and get out of here
(yue)快啲走吖
(en)Hurry up and go
(yue)我都想快啲走啊！
(en)I want to leave too!
(yue)所以媽媽你快啲出嚟吖！
(en)So, Mom, get out quickly!
(yue)你唔好再嘥時間
(en)Stop wasting time
(yue)媽媽啲腳壓斷咗
(en)Mom’s legs are crushed
(yue)就算真係拉到我出嚟
我都已經走唔郁
(en)Even if you pull me out, I can’t move
(yue)明唔明啊？
(en)Do you understand?
(yue)係噉嘅，我就孭住你走！
(en)If that’s the case, I’ll carry you on my back!
(yue)點解你呢個仔成日都唔肯聽媽媽嘅説話？
(en)Why do you never listen to your mother?
(yue)係咪我嘅遺言你都唔肯聽啊？
(en)Are you even going to ignore my final words?
(yue)米卡莎
(en)Mikasa
(yue)唔得！
(en)No!
(yue)就係噉落去我哋都會…
(en)If this goes on, we’ll all...
(yue)漢尼斯
(en)Hannes
(yue)你快啲幫我帶佢哋兩個走啊
(en)Quickly, take both of them and go
(yue)咁睇小我，搞到好難堪啊，卡露拉
(en)Don’t underestimate me, Carla, you’re making this awkward
(yue)你哋三個都會冇事嘅
(en)The three of you will be fine
(yue)我而家就去殺咗嗰個巨人
(en)I’ll kill that Titan right now
(yue)唔好啊！唔好去啊！
(en)No! Don’t go!
(yue)到底我應該即刻救走嗰兩個細路
定係趁呢個機會報答恩情呢？
(en)Should I save the two kids right now
or take this chance to repay my debt?
(yue)喂，漢尼斯，快啲放低我吖！
(en)Hey, Hannes, put me down now!
(yue)好多謝你
(en)Thank you so much
(yue)媽媽未走㗎
(en)Mom’s still there
(yue)媽媽！
(en)Mom!
(yue)艾倫、米卡莎
(en)Eren, Mikasa
(yue)要生存落去啊！
(en)You have to survive!
(yue)唔好走吖…
(en)Don’t leave...
(yue)唔好啊！
(en)No!
(yue)嗰一日，人類記返起…
(en)That day, humanity remembered...
(yue)一直畀佢哋支配嘅恐懼
(en)The fear that had always ruled over them
(yue)同由如韞喺鳥籠入面嘅…
(en)And the humiliation of being trapped in a birdcage-like state...
(yue)屈辱
(en)Humiliation
(yue)（待續）
(en)(To be continued)
(yue)（預告）
(en)(Preview)
(yue)西甘希娜淪陷
(en)The Fall of Shiganshina
(yue)人類可以做嘅事
(en)All humanity can do
(yue)只有祈禱、慘叫同埋死
(en)Is pray, scream, and die
(yue)只有艾倫一個下定決心
(en)Only Eren has resolved
(yue)誓要報仇
(yue)《那一天：西甘希娜淪陷2》
(en)To take revenge
(en)“That Day: The Fall of Shiganshina Part 2”